Hi, I'm JC Ko. I'm a legislator in Taiwan and professor at National Taiwan University.
Email spam costs $20 billion a year, but that's just the beginning. We're entering the age of
AI agents. Agents that book flights, negotiate deals, and coordinate workflows. And they all
need email. The internet's most universal, most human-readable protocol. Now imagine millions of
AI agents emailing millions of other AI agents. Spam doesn't just double, it explodes. When AI
spams AI, traditional filters are useless. We need something fundamentally different.
We need an attention market where every message carries economic weight.
That's what we built. This is The Diplomat, powered by Chainlink CRE.
you
Email is the most human-readable record of communication. Basemail makes it work across
Web 2, Web 3, and the agentic Web 4. And with Chainlink CRE powering The Diplomat,
we now have real-time AI arbitration for every message. This isn't just spam filtering. This
is communication economics for the age of AI agents. Thank you to the Chainlink team.